A Guide to the Bailey-Law Collection, 1825-1971
Special Collections, Virginia Tech
- SERIES II. HAROLD H. BAILEY PAPERS, 1910-1967
  - Subseries D. Publications, 1913-1947
    - The Birds of Virginia sales book, 1913-1929 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - The Birds of Virginia promotional material, [1913] (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Bulletin of the Bailey Museum and Library of Natural History sample issues, correspondence and lists, 1924-1947, n.d. (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Subseries E. Rockbridge Alum Springs, 1945-1964
    - Flyway lake, 1948-1954 (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Game and fish, 1945-1962, n.d. (Box 14, Folder 1-2)
    - Land acquisition, 1949-1953 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Naturalists portrait project, 1955-1964, n.d. (Box 14, Folder 4-5)
    - Separates in the Harold H. Bailey Ornithological Library and Museum, Index to, n.d., [in 2 parts] (Box 14, Folder 6-7)
    - General topics, 1947-1959, n.d. (Box 14, Folder 8)
- SERIES III. NATURALISTS BIOGRAPHICAL FILES, 1825-1971
  - Subseries A. Numerical Files, 1825-1970
    - #1-15 (Box 14, Folder 9)
      - #1 - Hathaway, Harry S., 1913-1930, n.d.
      - #2 - Pennock, Charles J., 1913-1931, n.d.
      - #3 - Carryl, F. M., 1920
      - #4 - Harper, Francis, 1929-1937
      - #5 - Squires, Karl, 1929, n.d.
      - #6 - Swainson, William, 1830
      - #7 - Forbush, E. H., 1914-1928
      - #8 - Richmond, Charles W., 1895-1928
      - #9 - Bangs, Outram, 1924
      - #10 - Simpson, Charles T., 1923-1932
      - #11 - Redick, L. L., 1925
      - #12 - Saunders, W. E., 1890-1938, n.d.
      - #13 - Kennard, Frederic H., 1915-1924
      - #14 - Bull, D. Bernard, 1924-1960
      - #15 - Keyes, Charles R., 1911-1924
    - #16-29 (Box 14, Folder 10)
      - #16 - Deane, Ruthven, 1903-1929, n.d.
      - #17 - Van Hyning, T., 1920-1946
      - #18 - Coale, Henry K., 1915-1924
      - #19 - Ramsden, Charles T., 1924
      - #20 - Methes, K. B., 1923, n.d.
      - #21 - Gifford, E. W., 1923
      - #22 - Treganza, A. O., 1913-1923, n.d.
      - #23 - Fairchild, David, 1923-1963
      - #24 - Stephens, Frank, 1923-1930
      - #25 - Davis, Henry W., 1922-1930
      - #26 - Still, Donald, 1920
      - #27 - Jackson, Hartley, 1923-1929
      - #28 - Brimley, C. S., 1923
      - #29 - Smyth, Thomas, 1923
    - #30-42 (Box 14, Folder 11)
      - #30 - Webb, Walter F., 1894-1946
      - #31 - Cantwell, George G. Blaine, 1918-1938
      - #32 - Peyton, L. G., 1919-1935
      - #33 - Cole, John L., 1921
      - #34 - Smith, Austin Paul, 1914-1931
      - #35 - Dickey, Donald R., 1921-1923
      - #36 - Littlejohn, Chase, 19191-1930
      - #37 - Wood, James, 1921
      - #38 - Murphey, Eugene, 1922-1952
      - #39 - Sherwood, Jack, 1923
      - #40 - Wolfe, L. R., 1922-1953
      - #41 - Eckstrom, Paul, 1914-1942
      - #42 - Thomas, Antonette K., 1919
    - #43-54 (Box 14, Folder 12)
      - #43 - Price, W. W., 1920
      - #44 - Quillin, Roy, 1919-1940
      - #45 - Fuller, R., 1919
      - #46 - Johnson, James O., 1920, n.d.
      - #47 - Brooks, Allan, 1936-1941, n.d.
      - #48 - Over, William H., 1917-1923
      - #49 - Dupond, Ch., 1923
      - #50 - Henderson, A. D., 1922-1956
      - #51 - Bailey, Alfred M., 1919-1965
      - #52 - Collins, W. R., 1924
      - #53 - Norman, Ernest S., 1923-1930
      - #54 - Dear, L. S., 1923
    - #55-70 (Box 15, Folder 1)
      - #55 - Allen, Glover, 1917-1937
      - #56 - Meyers, Harold, 1918
      - #57 - Batchelder, Charles, 1882-1937
      - #58 - Cassin, John, 1852
      - #59 - Peters, James S., 1923-1950
      - #60 - Friedrich, George W., 1920
      - #61 - Donahue, Ralph J., 1919
      - #62 - Archee, Rowland, 1920-1930
      - #63 - Handley, Charles O., 1920-1921
      - #64 - Arthur, Stanley Clisby, 1920-1929
      - #65 - Maynard, C. J., 1911-1924
      - #66 - McLaren, William, 1918
      - #67 - Loring, J. Alden, 1914-1921
      - #68 - Hatch, Delos, 1921
      - #69 - Sharples - R. P., 1921-1922
      - #70 - Bancroft, Griffing, 1920-1925
    - #71-92 (Box 15, Folder 2)
      - #71 - Lyon, W. I., 1922
      - #72 - Jacobs, J. Warren, 1922-1941
      - #73 - Ingersoll, A. M., 1895-1921
      - #74 - Kimball, H. H., 1920
      - #75 - Vars, Harold N., 1920
      - #76 - Pember, Karl Albrecht, 1921
      - #77 - La Gonce, John Oliver, 1921
      - #78 - Edwards, H. Arden, n.d.
      - #79 - Gordon, Jack G., 1919
      - #80 - More, R. L., 1913-1954, n.d.
      - #81 - Butler, Ernest A., 1914-1919
      - #82 - Munro, J. A., 1916-1937
      - #83 - Walker, Ernest P., 1918-1965
      - #84 - Bradbury, W. C., 1922
      - #85 - Meyer, G. Ralph, 1922
      - #86 - Pemberton, J. R., 1921
      - #87 - Metzger, Chas. T., 1927
      - #88 - Jones, Lynds, 1928-1937
      - #89 - Alexander, W. B., 1926
      - #90 - Hubbard, Ralph, 1920-1924
      - #91 - Maupin, W. L., n.d.
      - #92 - Weber, J. A., 1923-1950
    - #93-107 (Box 15, Folder 3)
      - #93 - Wilkinson, C. J., 1913
      - #94 - Henninger, W. F., 1913-1914
      - #95 - Poole, Earl L., 1895-1945
      - #96 - Massey, Herbert, 1913
      - #97 - Winslow, A. M., n.d.
      - #98 - Gardiner, C. B., 1913
      - #99 - Norris, Joseph Parke, 1894-[1926?]
      - #100 - Knapp, Elmer S., 1913
      - #101 - Pearson, T. Gilbert, 1915-1936
      - #102 - Kenworthey, E. M., 1914
      - #103 - Saunders, Aretas A., 1914
      - #104 - Miller, W., 1910-1923
      - #105 - Barnes, R. M., 1914-1945, n.d.
      - #106 - Ridgeway, Robert, 1887-1914, n.d.
      - #107 - Raine, Walter, 1895-1914
    - #108-121 (Box 15, Folder 4)
      - #108 - Grinnell, Joseph, 1913-1966, n.d.
      - #109 - Dwight, Jonathan Jr., 1914-1919
      - #110 - Knight, O. Willis, 1913
      - #111 - Warren, Ed. R., 1913-1937
      - #112 - Trescot, E. B., 1914
      - #113 - Bailey, Florence M., 1914-1942
      - #114 - Grant, W. W., n.d.
      - #115 - Harlow, Richard, 1914-1962
      - #116 - Beers, H. W., 1906
      - #117 - Tyler, John G., 1914-1964
      - #118 - Smith, Franklin J., 1909-1948
      - #119 - Brimley, H. H., 1913
      - #120 - Hollister, N., 1911-1914
      - #121 - Silliman, O. P., 1913-1915
    - #122-135 (Box 15, Folder 5)
      - #122 - Riley, J. H., 1913-1924
      - #123 - Carr, Chas. F., n.d.
      - #124 - Brownell, L. W., 1913, n.d.
      - #125 - Stone, Wilmer, 1914-1939, n.d.
      - #126 - Bent, A. C., 1912-1939
      - #127 - Willard, F. C., 1914
      - #128 - Newbury, F. E., 1894-1914
      - #129 - Viquesney, J. A., 1914
      - #130 - King, W. W., 1913
      - #131 - Adams, Benjamin, 1913
      - #132 - Hutchinson, W. F., 1913-1916
      - #133 - Henshaw, Samuel, 1913-1923
      - #134 - Bayne, M. S., 1913
      - #135 - Mayor, Alfred G., 1921-1922
    - #136-158 (Box 15, Folder 6)
      - #136 - Rothschild, Baron Lionel, 1937
      - #137 - Langevin, Elmer, 1921-1946
      - #138 - Fischer, Otto A., 1926
      - #139 - Eiche, August, 1923
      - #140 - Bolt, Benjamin F., 1923
      - #141 - Layne, J. Gregg, 1913
      - #142 - Fordyce, George L., 1913
      - #143 - Sherman, A. R., 1913
      - #144 - Wilby, Donald, 1913
      - #145 - Love, Guy, 1913-1914
      - #146 - Giles, R. I., 1913
      - #147 - Ells, George P., 1913
      - #148 - Hersey, L. Ray, 1913
      - #149 - Jackson, Ralph W., 1913-1957
      - #150 - Burns, Frank L., 1911
      - #151 - Hastings, Otto C., 1913-1917
      - #152 - Bales, B. R., 1913-1916
      - #153 - Hodgdon, A. L., 1913
      - #154 - Palmer, William M., 1913
      - #155 - Miller, Richard F., 1913-1952
      - #156 - Chambers, W. Lee, 1913-1920
      - #157 - Swales, B. H., 1913-1920
      - #158 - Beal, F. E. L., 1913, n.d.
    - #159-171 (Box 15, Folder 7)
      - #159 - Bishop, Louis B., 1913-1941, n.d.
      - #160 - Rockwell, Robert B., 1913
      - #161 - Childs, John Lewis, 1913-1916, n.d.
      - #162 - Ericksen, W. J., 1913-1915
      - #163 - Stuart, H. C., 1913
      - #164 - Helme, A. H., 1911-1931
      - #165 - Bailey, Harold B., 1887-1952
      - #166 - Chamberlain, C. W., 1912-1929
      - #167 - Mershon, William B., 1913-1929
      - #168 - Rhoads, S. N., 1913
      - #169 - Lucas, F. A., 1889-1913
      - #170 - Purdie, Henry, 1908
      - #171 - Benners, Archie and G. B., 1913-1914
    - #172-185 (Box 15, Folder 8)
      - #172 - Barnard, Oscar E., 1913
      - #173 - Lings, G. S., 1913
      - #174 - Jackson, T. H., 1913-1920
      - #175 - Mann, William Hodges, 1913
      - #176 - Wheeler, H. E., 1913-1952
      - #177 - Vest, O. B., 1913
      - #178 - Sage, J. H., 1905-1917
      - #179 - Cooke, Wells, 1909-1914
      - #180 - Fisher, A. K., 1911-1948, n.d.
      - #181 - Dutcher, William, 1901-1910
      - #182 - Bragg, Laura, 1914
      - #183 - Drowne, F. P., 1910
      - #184 - Burnham, John B., 1912
      - #185 - Sowers, H. S., 1914-1918
    - #186-194 (Box 15, Folder 9)
      - #186 - Darlington, E. J., 1914
      - #187 - Wheeler, Roswell, 1914
      - #188 - Chapman, Frank, 1913-1964
      - #189 - Brown, Edgar J., 1913-1969
      - #190 - Beck, R. H., 1918-1960, n.d.
      - #191 - Walker, Alex, 1918-1960, n.d.
      - #192 - Worthington, W. W., 1902-1920, n.d.
      - #193 - Schutze, H. E., 1915
      - #194 - Wood, Casey, 1920-1940
    - #195-202 (Box 15, Folder 10)
      - #195 - Warren, H., 1913
      - #196 - Moffat, Earl, 1914
      - #197 - Flint, H. W., 1915
      - #198 - Brandt, H. W., 1917-1955, n.d.
      - #199 - Robinson, Wirt, 1917-1924, n.d.
      - #200 - Sornborger, J. D., 1915
      - #201 - Stephens, T. C., 1916-1929
      - #202 - Hughes, J. T., 1916
    - #203-219 (Box 15, Folder 11)
      - #203 - Cleaves, Howard, 1917-1961
      - #204 - Evans, Logan I., 1919
      - #205 - Du Bois, A. D., 1918-1943
      - #206 - Oberholser, Harry C., 1924-1961, n.d.
      - #207 - Coombs, Edward S., 1927
      - #208 - Townsend, Charles H., 1898-1941
      - #209 - Saunders, W. H., 1915
      - #210 - Palmer, S. C., 1914-1915
      - #211 - Ruthven, Alexander, 1917
      - #212 - Lunsford, Irving, 1918
      - #213 - French, George D., 1917
      - #214 - Gruber, E., 1906
      - #215 - Pinney, W. W., 1914
      - #216 - De Camps, E. J., 1941
      - #217 - Reger, G. B., 1918
      - #218 - Kirkwood, F. C., 1918
      - #219 - Laurent, Philip, 1917-1922
    - #220-230 (Box 15, Folder 12)
      - #220 - Irving, F. N., 1915-1958
      - #221 - Dickey, S. S., 1914-1916
      - #222 - Ganier, A. F., 1916
      - #223 - Harrowes, D. E., 1916
      - #224 - Miller, Gerrit, 1917-1956
      - #225 - Huber, Wharton, 1916
      - #226 - Peet, Max M., 1915-1948
      - #227 - Emerson, Otto W., 1908-1926
      - #228 - Tufts, Robie W., 1915-1936
      - #229 - Burtch, Verdie, 1914-1946, n.d.
      - #230 - Labarthe, J., n.d.
    - #231-246 (Box 15, Folder 13)
      - #231 - Munroe, Kirk (Mrs.), 1921
      - #232 - Job, Herbert K., 1917
      - #233 - Smith, A. Russell, 1918
      - #234 - Jewett, Stanley G., 1918-1941
      - #235 - Daniel, John W. Jr., 1895-1919
      - #236 - Griffen, B. S., 1918
      - #237 - Case, Clifford M., 1918
      - #238 - Dice, Lee R., 1945, n.d.
      - #239 - Hedges, Charles F., 1924
      - #240 - Mailliard, Joseph, 1905-1938, n.d.
      - #241 - Carter, James B., 1915
      - #242 - West, Charles S., 1919
      - #243 - Carpenter, N. K., 1918-1955, n.d.
      - #244 - Wood, Norman A., 1925-1942, n.d.
      - #245 - Norris, Joseph P., 1914
      - #246 - Mousley, H., 1919
    - #247-263 (Box 16, Folder 1)
      - #247 - Gammell, R. E., 1928-1929
      - #248 - Withey, George L., 1924
      - #249 - Snow, Henry A., 1927, n.d.
      - #250 - Wetmore, Alexander, 1924-1967, n.d.
      - #251 - Stansell, Sidney S. S., 1917
      - #252 - Perry, Elton, 1924
      - #253 - Murie, O. J., 1914-1954
      - #254 - Thayer, John E., 1911-1926
      - #255 - Herricks, Francis H., 1924-1938
      - #256 - Guion, George S., 1912-1914
      - #257 - Evans, J. Harrold, 1911
      - #258 - Ekstrom, Fannie H., 1920-1944
      - #259 - Purdy, William B., 1920
      - #260 - Skinner, E. R., 1913
      - #261 - Ferneyhough, J. Bowie, 1913-1948
      - #262 - Worthington, Charles C., 1913
      - #263 - Daggett, Frank S., 1895-1920
    - #264-281 (Box 16, Folder 2)
      - #264 - Agassiz, Louis, 1851-1893, n.d.
      - #265 - Bonaparte, Charles Lucien, 1825, n.d.
      - #266 - Bachman, John, 1852, n.d.
      - #267 - Hazard, R. G., 1913-1917
      - #268 - Hunt, Edwin B., 1915
      - #269 - Dexter, Lewis, 1915
      - #270 - Smyth, Ellison A. Jr., 1920-1939
      - #271 - McIlwain, H. R., 1912
      - #272 - Knickerbocker, C. H., 1913
      - #273 - Sugden, J. W., 1919-1933
      - #274 - Querriam, Henry, n.d.
      - #275 - Bailey, William Lloyd, n.d.
      - #276 - Preble, Edward A., 1949, n.d.
      - #277 - Griscom, Ludlow, 1913
      - #278 - Baird, Spencer F., 1864-1886, n.d.
      - #279 - Jenney, Charles F., 1915
      - #280 - Bartsch, Paul, 1916
      - #281 - Harris, Harry, n.d.
    - #282-293 (Box 16, Folder 3)
      - #282 - Mearns, Edgar A., 1913
      - #283 - Cooper, J. G., 1887
      - #284 - Roberts, Thomas S., n.d.
      - #285 - Phillips, John C., n.d.
      - #286 - Henderson, Junius, 1924
      - #287 - Armstrong, Edward D., 1926, n.d.
      - #288 - Ellis, Ralph Jr., 1929-1945
      - #289 - Skinner, Milton P., 1929
      - #290 - Brown, Lewis B., 1913
      - #291 - Wilson, Gaines, 1954, n.d.
      - #292 - Barbour, Thomas, 1923-1944
      - #293 - Williams, Robert W., 1920-1930, n.d.
    - #294-299 (Box 16, Folder 4)
      - #294 - Rossingnol, Gilbert R., 1921-1956
      - #295 - Wayne, Arthur T., 1924
      - #296 - Fuertes, Louis Agassiz, 1921
      - #297 - Finley, William L., 1930-1953
      - #298 - Camp, R. D., 1928
      - #299 - Fleming, J. H., 1930
    - #300-318 (Box 16, Folder 5)
      - #300 - Rowan, William, 1929-1952
      - #301 - Sprunt, Alex Jr., 1931-1951
      - #302 - Bowles, J. Hooper, 1929-1931
      - #303 - Hall, E. Raymond, 1930-1958
      - #304 - Danforth, Stuart, 1931
      - #305 - Sanford, C. C., n.d.
      - #306 - Priest, Cecil, 1931
      - #307 - Brockway, Arthur W., 1931-1941
      - #308 - Abbott, G. Allen, 1924
      - #309 - Richie, Sanford, 1930
      - #310 - Havemeyer, Henry O., 1931
      - #311 - Smith, Wilbur F., 1931
      - #312 - [empty]
      - #313 - Vaughn, Harry S., 1931
      - #314 - Benedict, H. Y., 1929
      - #315 - Allen, Arthur A., 1931-1943
      - #316 - Brower, Charles D., 1929-1944
      - #317 - Van Rossem, A. J., 1930
      - #318 - Emilio, S. Gilbert, 1930
    - #319-341 (Box 16, Folder 6)
      - #319 - Lamb, Chester C., 1930-1962, n.d.
      - #320 - Gould, Joseph, 1930-1945, n.d.
      - #321 - Farley, Frank L., 1929-1949
      - #322 - Small, John K., 1924-1929
      - #323 - Crandall, Lee S., 1929-1951
      - #324 - Hine, James S., 1929
      - #325 - Aschemeyer, C. R., 1929
      - #326 - Swanson, Gustav, 1931
      - #327 - Murphy, Robert, 1929-1954
      - #328 - Goode, G. Brown, 1892-1893
      - #329 - Breninger, George F., 1897
      - #330 - Bryant, Walter, 1893
      - #331 - Bendire, Charles, 1896
      - #332 - Doe, Charles F., 1896
      - #333 - Anthony, A. W., 1897, n.d.
      - #334 - Peabody, P. B., 1896
      - #335 - Taylor, Harry R., 1896
      - #336 - Wright, Frank S., 1896
      - #337 - Cumming, Robert C., 1896
      - #338 - Cass, Charles S., 1896
      - #339 - Browne, F. C., 1894
      - #340 - Gilds, Francis C., 1895
      - #341 - Dalgleish, John I., 1894
    - #342-358 (Box 16, Folder 7)
      - #342 - Ralph, W. S., 1894-1895
      - #343 - Worthen, Charles K., 1894
      - #344 - McIlhenny, E. A., 1894-1929
      - #345 - Shields, A. M., 1895
      - #346 - McGregor, Rich C., 1931
      - #347 - Rich, Walter H., 1931-1948
      - #348 - McMurtrie, Richard, 1895
      - #349 - Hardy, Manly, 1894-1947
      - #350 - Crandall, Chauncy W., 1896-1920
      - #351 - Elliot, E. A. Savage, 1895
      - #352 - Kuschel, M., 1895
      - #353 - Foster, L. S., 1894
      - #354 - Fairchild, Herman, 1930-1943
      - #355 - Cook, George L., 1929
      - #356 - Webster, Frank B., 1896
      - #357 - Langley, S. P., 1898, n.d.
      - #358 - True, F. W., 1894
    - #359-361 (Box 16, Folder 8)
      - #359 - Ligon, J. Stokley, 1928-1960
      - #360 - Willett, George, 1920-1943, n.d.
      - #361 - Dury, Charles, 1926-1933
    - #362-372 (Box 16, Folder 9)
      - #362 - McAtee, W. L., 1923-1962
      - #363 - Peck, Morton E., 1929
      - #364 - Roig, Mario Sanchez, 1929
      - #365 - Fryklund, P. O., 1928
      - #366 - Savany, Walter B., 1927
      - #367 - Hemphill, Frederick A., 1931
      - #368 - Black, J. D., 1932
      - #369 - Palmer, T. S., 1932-1957
      - #370 - Swarth, Harry S., 1929-1931
      - #371 - Evermann, Barton W., 1931
      - #372 - Laing, Hamilton M., 1932-1950
    - #373-390 (Box 16, Folder 10)
      - #373 - Burleigh, Thomas D., 1935-1948, n.d.
      - #374 - Harlow, J. Earl, 1925
      - #375 - Neilson, James A., 1923
      - #376 - Heath, Donald, 1914
      - #377 - Brooking, A. M., 1924
      - #378 - Wish, F. H. L., 1932
      - #379 - Carber, Jno. D., 1927
      - #380 - Weston, Francis M., 1929
      - #381 - Ray, Milton S., 1923-1946
      - #382 - Sherman, H. B., 1927-1951
      - #383 - Bunyard, P. F., 1932
      - #384 - Yngstroem, M. C. I., 1930
      - #385 - Thurston, Henry, 1921-1951
      - #386 - Tomkins, Ivan R., 1932
      - #387 - Smith, W. A., 1932-1948
      - #388 - Hewitt, A., n.d.
      - #389 - Barlow, George R., 1931
      - #390 - Figgins, J. D., 1923-1937, n.d.
    - #391-410 (Box 16, Folder 11)
      - #391 - Kirksey, T. M., 1934
      - #392 - Brown, D. E., 1936
      - #393 - Price, A. E., 1936
      - #394 - Richter, C. H., 1933-1945
      - #395 - Peck, George D., 1934
      - #396 - Zuercher, C. F., 1935
      - #397 - Overington, R. Bruce, 1935
      - #398 - Walters, Robinson C., 1935-1937
      - #399 - Jones, F. M., 1934
      - #400 - Sampson, W. B., 1934-1941
      - #401 - Walsh, Lester L., n.d.
      - #402 - Sperry, Charles C., 1933
      - #403 - Wyman, L. E., 1920
      - #404 - Brooks, W. Sprague, 1923
      - #405 - Ravenel, W. deC., 1920-1931
      - #406 - Sheak, W. H., 1921
      - #407 - Ranson, Robert, 1926
      - #408 - Long, W. S., 1933
      - #409 - Bailey, Bernard, 1935
      - #410 - Wing, Leonard W., 1931-1947
    - #411-425 (Box 16, Folder 12)
      - #411 - Marshall, Arthur P., 1933
      - #412 - Cassino, Samuel L., 1882, n.d.
      - #413 - Pope, Clifford H., 1937-1939
      - #414 - Pierce, Wright M., 1930-1936
      - #415 - Baker, Jack D., 1937
      - #416 - Rowley, J. Stuart, 1937
      - #417 - Baillie, James C., 1935
      - #418 - Howell, A. B., 1956, n.d.
      - #419 - Hill, John Eric, 1937
      - #420 - Dille, Fred M., 1938-1948, n.d.
      - #421 - Taverner, Percy A., 1937-1946, n.d.
      - #422 - Turcotte, William, 1933
      - #423 - Bulley, Rex, 1926, n.d.
      - #424 - O'Reiley, Ralph Jr., 1938
      - #425 - Unglish, Will E., 1936
    - #426-432 (Box 16, Folder 13)
      - #426 - Bartch, Paul, 1937-1960, n.d.
      - #427 - Fleming, J. H., 1939
      - #428 - Eyerdam, Walter J., 1938-1960
      - #429 - Todd, W. E., 1939-1955
      - #430 - Wirz, J. J., 1940
      - #431 - Richards, T. W., 1940-1952
      - #432 - Abbott, Clinton G., 1939-1942
    - #433-445 (Box 17, Folder 1)
      - #433 - Arvey, M. Dale, 1940, n.d.
      - #434 - Steinbeck, W. P., 1940
      - #435 - Hurley, John B., 1940-1962
      - #436 - [empty]
      - #437 - Haley, E. L. R., 1939-1946
      - #438 - Hagenbeck, Lorenz, 1939, n.d.
      - #439 - Wood, A. A., 1939
      - #440 - Kirk, George L., 1938
      - #441 - Arman, Isaac F., 1939
      - #442 - Racey, Kenneth, 1938-1956
      - #443 - Pope, E. F., 1941, n.d.
      - #444 - Cherrie, George K., 1939-1947, n.d.
      - #445 - McIlwaine, William B., 1938-1950
    - #446-461 (Box 17, Folder 2)
      - #446 - Duprey, H. F., 1938-1943
      - #447 - Roberts, Thomas S., 1938
      - #448 - Moore, Joseph C., 1941
      - #449 - Meyer, Fred P., 1958
      - #450 - Twining, Howard, 1938-1939
      - #451 - Clay, Charles I., 1940-1958, n.d.
      - #452 - Montagna, William, 1940-1941
      - #453 - Sutton, George M., 1940
      - #454 - Vandervort, Charles C., 1940
      - #455 - Doutt, J. Kenneth, 1941
      - #456 - Mason, Robert F., 1941
      - #457 - Townsend, Charles W., 1913-1920
      - #458 - Palsson, William F., 1940
      - #459 - Hamilton, William J., 1941-1943
      - #460 - Starr, F. A. E., 1941
      - #461 - Agassis, A., 1895-1897
    - #462-477 (Box 17, Folder 3)
      - #462 - Hitchcock, Frank H., 1899-1905
      - #463 - Fannin, J., 1891
      - #464 - Stefansson, Vilhjalmur, 1931-1940
      - #465 - Jordan, David Starr, 1897
      - #466 - Hornaday, William T., 1897-1937
      - #467 - Nelson, E. W., 1922-1928
      - #468 - Wegeforth, Harry M., 1937
      - #469 - Evans, Cerinda W., 1948-1968
      - #470 - Allen, J. A., 1905
      - #471 - Seton, Ernest T., 1914-1924
      - #472 - Bannerman, David, 1923
      - #473 - Belding, Linan, 1888
      - #474 - Osborn, Henry Fairfield, 1915-1941
      - #475 - Grinnell, George Bird, 1905
      - #476 - Nolan, Edward J., 1912
      - #477 - Merriam, C. Hart, 1897-1943
    - #478-488 (Box 17, Folder 4)
      - #478 - Flower, Stanley S., 1929
      - #479 - Biglow, Edward F., 1930
      - #480 - Poulsson, T. H., 1930
      - #481 - Roosevelt, Kermit, 1924-1935
      - #482 - Nicholson, Ray H., n.d.
      - #483 - Hammond, Edward K., 1942
      - #484 - Cole, Leon J., 1941-1948, n.d.
      - #485 - Fearnehough, N. V., 1940-1945
      - #486 - Griepentrog, Elmer L., 1936
        Scope and Contents note
        [envelope only]
      - #487 - Heaton, Harry L., 1937-1940
      - #488 - Brazil, David, 1939-1942
    - #489-496 (Box 17, Folder 5)
      - #489 - Ford, Edward R. 1936-1950
      - #490 - Eschenburg, Rodney 1939
      - #491 - Engstrom, Otto Ed. 1938
      - #492 - Maguire, W. S. 1938-1948
      - #493 - Feathers, Dawson A. 1938
      - #494 - Birkholz, Clifford 1938
      - #495 - Pack, Arthur N. 1933
      - #496 - Taylor, Horace 1940
    - #497-514 (Box 17, Folder 6)
      - #497 - Goodpaster, Woodrow, 1939
      - #498 - Brooks, James C., 1958
      - #499 - Frazier, J. F., 1935-1937
      - #500 - Herdman, W. A., 1909
      - #501 - Wigglesworth, Edward, 1929
      - #502 - Morse, Edward S., 1927
      - #503 - Huxley, Julian, 1920
      - #504 - Brown, J. Stanley, 1897
      - #505 - Wadsworth, W. A., 1916
      - #506 - Bergerson, Birger, 1937
      - #507 - James, Arthur C., 1926
      - #508 - Newcombe, C. F., 1890
      - #509 - Dixon, J. B., 1936
      - #510 - Cohen, Donald A., 1936-1948
      - #511 - Benson, John T., 1943
      - #512 - Snyder, W. E., 1922
      - #513 - Stone, D. D., 1933
      - #514 - McMullen, Turner E., 1938-1954
    - #515-527 (Box 17, Folder 7)
      - #515 - Ball, Stanley C., 1942-1944
      - #516 - Salt, W. Ray, 1940-1943
      - #517 - Pierce, Fred J., 1942
      - #518 - Henderson, W. W., 1942
      - #519 - Gudger, E. W., 1927
      - #520 - Thwing, Charles F., 1926
      - #521 - Lings, G. H., n.d.
      - #522 - Nichols, John T., 1921-1957
      - #523 - Harrison, Ed. N., 1946-1968
      - #524 - Stephan, Joseph A., n.d.
      - #525 - Waters, Robinson C., 1935
      - #526 - Jensen, J. K., 1942-1945
      - #527 - Taylor, Walter P., 1950-1951
    - #528-533 (Box 17, Folder 8)
      - #528 - Gross, Alfred O., 1948-1968, n.d.
      - #529 - Conover, H. B., 1949
      - #530 - Wise, Jennings C., 1958-1966, n.d.
      - #531 - Vorhies, Charles T., 1949-1950
      - #532 - Stoddard, Herbert L., 1925-1964
      - #533 - Rooney, James, 1946-1953
    - #534-550 (Box 17, Folder 9)
      - #534 - Rand, A. L., 1946
      - #535 - Swenk, Myson H., 1919-1925
      - #536 - Morse, Frank E., 1936
      - #537 - Cosby, Manvall, 1925
      - #538 - Abbott, Jacob B., 1933-1936